{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Power Washing Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40008/":{"taskOID":40008,"originalTaskOID":40008,"setID":332,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1217,"questionDisplayText":"Description of area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the area or item(s) needing power washing.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5673,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Side of building","answerDisplayText":"Side of building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway/sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway/sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4611,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio or deck","answerDisplayText":"Patio or deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4577,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2978,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heavy equipment","answerDisplayText":"Heavy equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5399,"questionDisplayText":"Why Power Washing is Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need power/pressure washing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1217,"questionDisplayText":"Description of area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the area or item(s) needing power washing.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5673,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Side of building","answerDisplayText":"Side of building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway/sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway/sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4611,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio or deck","answerDisplayText":"Patio or deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4577,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2978,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heavy equipment","answerDisplayText":"Heavy equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5673,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Side of building","answerDisplayText":"Side of building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6734,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway/sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway/sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4611,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio or deck","answerDisplayText":"Patio or deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4577,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Parking area","answerDisplayText":"Parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2978,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heavy equipment","answerDisplayText":"Heavy equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5399,"questionDisplayText":"Why Power Washing is Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need power/pressure washing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4894,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Prepare for painting","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202484,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove oil or grease ","answerDisplayText":"Remove oil or grease ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5175,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","answerDisplayText":"Remove pollution and fuel emission residue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5167,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","answerDisplayText":"Remove mineral or hard water deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove mold or moss","answerDisplayText":"Remove mold or moss","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40008/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40008,"taskName":"Exterior Surfaces - Powerwashing","taskDescription":"Powerwash Exterior Surfaces","xmTaskDescriptor":"Power Washing Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":75,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"exterior power powerwash surfaces wash","textMessagingName":"Powerwash","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically used to clean decks, siding, concrete, masonry \u0026 other surfaces.  This category is for powerwashing only.  Note separate category for powerwashing \u0026 applying sealant.","rolloverShortDesc":"Cleaning with a high-pressure sprayer.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Powerwash Exterior Surfaces.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Power Washing Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Home \u0026 Siding Power Wash","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Powerwash Exterior Surface","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Exterior Surfaces - Powerwashing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Powerwashing Project","urlName":"Exterior-Surfaces-Powerwashing","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Power Washing Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"exterior,power,powerwash,surfaces,wash,aluminum,clean,deck,washing,siding,pressure,masonry,concrete","emcCategoryOid":-14980,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":332,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}